Mom, I still don't know
how this happened to you.
I got this inside.
Looks like a camera.
Are you sure that's the Korean
we're looking for?
- Yes, Sir.
- Who is he talking to?
Dad, that's Theresa.
She's the woman Jin Ho
wants to capture.
I also want to meet the man
you brought into this group.
Stop this nonsense!
Is this really how you are
when I'm not here?
Is this how you handle
this place?
Andrew is going through
something heavy right now.
Call him.
Where's Andrew?
He's preparing things
to bring to the hospital
for Mommy Rebecca.
"Mommy?"
I guess I should get used
to calling her that
since things are getting better
between me and Andrew.
[OBB]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I guess you're back together.
That's good.
Congratulations to you.
Joey...
Thanks for being happy for us.
We're not yet official
but we both know that's where
it's heading, right?
You know, Joey...
I wish you'd find the person
meant for you too.
You know what?
I can help you with that.
I can introduce you
to some of my friends,
maybe you'll like one of them.
I'm not looking for a partner.
Are you sure?
Because I just want you
to be happy,
Just like us.
Just like me and Andrew.
Anyway, if you change your mind
or you need help,
I'll set you up, just tell me.
Okay, I have to go,
Andrew and I have something
to do.
Bye!
You're here.
- Andrew!
- We're about to leave.
Yes, let's go.
Why do you have my phone?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Nothing, I just wanted
to give it to you.
You might forget it.
Here.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Excuse me.
Okay.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Gosh, so arrogant!
[PHONE CHIMES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIGHT AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Go ahead and enjoy your coffee
because that'll be your last.
You're doomed.
[LIGHT AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho.
Joey...
You got me there.
Have a seat first.
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What happened to you?
Did you get into a fight?
Who did you fight?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPPING]
Got you.
So, you're quite
the ladies' man.
Let's see if Lisa will help you
when she finds out
you're two-timing her.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPPING]
It's nothing.
It's just work hazard.
That's why I wanted to see you.
I need to forget work
for a while.
Okay.
I thought you're going
to invite the others.
- Others?
- Yes.
Is Peter still
at the boarding house?
No...
Peter went to his province.
What about Andrew?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
He's with his girlfriend.
He has a girlfriend, really?
I mean...
All this time, I thought the
two of you will end up together.
No, never!
Uncle, wait!
Don't leave yet.
Uncle Andrew, we need your help.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, what is this?
I can't fix this.
Can you fix this?
Yes, Sir.
Thank you,
and if you can't fix it,
please tell my sister,
maybe she can have it fixed.
- Yes, Sir.
- Okay, problem solved.
- Anyway...
- And, Uncle...
we need your help too.
As just as much
as I wanna help you,
I really can't right now
because grandmother is alone
at the hospital.
I'm sorry.
But I promise when I return,
I'll help you.
Is that okay?
Okay, Uncle Andrew. Promise?
Promise.
Kiss grandmother for us, please.
I will.
- Anyway, I'll go, okay?
- Okay, take care!
Bye!
I'm really curious
if this still works,
maybe our old videos are here.
Maybe daddy can help us?
You know what? You stay here.
I'm going to order, my treat.
No, no, I will pay,
I invited you.
No, it's okay, my treat.
Stay there.
[PLEASANT AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPEAKING INAUDIBLY]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Kang Dae-Hyun.
He might betray us!
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
You are Kang Dae-Hyun, correct?
I just want to ask
a few questions.
[THUDS]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Stay here! Don't follow us!
I thought
he was with the police.
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad!
Didn't I tell you not to follow?
Dad, I was worried about you.
That Jin Ho is lucky.
He escaped.
[REVVING]
Dad, it'd better
if we leave now.
She's right, Miguel,
you two should leave.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Is that Delgado?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, please wear
this again, please.
Get the car,
let's go after him!
Don't, Dad!
Someone might recognize you!
Your daughter is right.
Go ahead, Miguel,
I'll handle this.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Where is he?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Berdugo...
would you know if Delgado's body
has already been released?
What are you saying, Matias?
I don't know.
It feels like I'm being haunted.
Haunted?
Matias, I don't have time
for your nonsense.
Sorry, Berdugo.
I think I saw Delgado.
What?
Where have you been?
I was chased.
Chased?
Yes.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Lisa, I have a problem.
The cops already know
who I really am.
What? How?
I don't know how.
But...
one of them called me
by my real name.
That's why I ran.
No, I really think
we're being followed.
I think something's wrong.
My gut feels different.
I knew it.
Someone was really following us,
and they were after you.
Another problem.
There's no problem, I got away.
- No one followed me here.
- Don't you get it?
I can't rely on you
if the police are following you.
I think it's best
if you stay here
and lay low for a while.
So you wanna keep me here
like a prisoner?
Yes.
I'd rather keep you here
than in prison.
And besides, I could
defend you from Berdugo
if he finds out about this.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma'am, I've prepared everything
Ma'am Rebecca needs.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'll bring it myself,
and I'll just call you
if I need anything else.
All right.
Sir Tomas, I'll go ahead.
Thank you.
Wait, Clarissa.
What is it, Sir?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why, Hon? Do you need something
from Clarissa?
Nothing, I just want
to ask her something.
Has your husband's body
been released?
Has he been buried?
Oh, yes.
What the progress?
Not yet.
But Chief told us
that he will help us
until Miguel's body is buried.
Maybe it will be released soon.
Well, if you need anything,
just let us know, okay?
We'll be happy to help.
Thank you so much.
- I'll go ahead.
- All right.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You don't need
to confront Jin Ho.
You're rushing into action
and without the support
of the department.
Sir, it's just that
the opportunity was there.
That's not an excuse.
Sorry, Sir.
I should have told you.
Good thing no one saw me,
otherwise, my cover of being
dead would be ruined.
My bosses are also asking me
if Miguel's body
has been released.
I just said it will be
released soon.
Yes, Sir, Is anyone looking
for my body?
Maybe that's what Berdugo
is thinking too.
It's not impossible
for the syndicate
to have doubts as long as they
don't see your body
and your burial.
Then, let's bury Miguel.
We'll stand by the story
that I'm dead?
Yes.
Thank you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SWEEPING]
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Peter!
You're up early.
Good morning, Aunt Beng.
- Good morning.
I already put soft drinks
and liquor in the fridge.
And the deliveries
are on their way.
Looks like you woke up
in a good mood, Peter.
Scary.
You're crazy!
You know, in the few days
I've been here,
I've realized a lot of things.
I've also learned a lot,
especially from you,
Auntie Beng.
And from you, Kit.
"Gobble, gobble, gobble",
said the turkey.
I think I know the point
of scenes like this!
This is exactly how shows go
when someone plans to leave.
There, like that, all dressed up
but no shoes yet.
Sentimental, thinking about
all the lessons learned
from other people's lives.
You're leaving, Peter?
You're going back to Manila?
You know, son...
We're happy that you're here,
and your brother and I are happy
that we helped you
with your problem.
So, that's okay.
Just promise us you'll be
careful in Manila, okay?
Thank you, Auntie Beng.
You, don't forget
what I told you, okay?
Of course, Peter.
I will be patient.
I will never give up
on the person I love.
I won't be like you.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
And not just that.
Learn to work hard
and help Auntie Bebeng
in the store
so it would somehow earn.
- Agree!
- Of course, Peter.
I love Auntie Bebeng so much.
Hey.
You're going to kill me.
[SIGHS]
Okay then, come on,
let's give this
a power group hug!
[GRUNTING]
Ah, wait, wait!
What is this?
Oh my, I'll never get married
because of you two.
The two of you are already
too much!
Put me down!
Too much love, Auntie?
No, headache! Down!
[GROANS]
I'll cook breakfast.
Come on, go inside!
Hey, inside!
Coming, coming!
Hurry up!
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
Condolence, Clarissa and Joey.
Thank you.
It's bad to thank someone
for sympathizing with the dead.
Yes.
Sorry, I just forgot.
Please sit down.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
It feels wrong, Mom.
Father isn't really dead.
Hush!
Someone might hear you.
But, Mom...
I really feel guilty.
We're fooling them all.
Once your father completes
his mission,
and takes down the syndicate,
I'm sure they'll understand us.
I just hope that time
comes soon
so we won't have to lie
to them anymore.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Our friends, Jake and Loy,
offered condolences.
I'm sorry.
You got dragged
into my problem too.
If this is the coffee shop,
then where could Berdugo's
drug factory be?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Could it be this?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS]
So, you take charge of Tirada
for now, okay?
Sure, Boss.
We got it covered.
I'm just fixing the script,
so we'll have something
to upload.
Then, we'll just bring
the bus here
to make it easier for you.
Okay, thank you.
Thanks also for visiting mommy.
It wasn't just her we visited.
You too, Boss.
How are you?
Hoping for the best.
But why are you alone now?
Where's your Zoey?
[CHUCKLES]
Are you irritated already?
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Or maybe it's another "Oey"
you want?
[GASPS]
Gasp.
Who?
Joey?
Come on, Kyle, that's fake news.
Instead of making up gossip,
why don't you just ask him?
- Who is it really? Like that.
- Yes, that's right?
[PHONE RINGING]
Oh, wait.
Hello? Yvette?
I'm going to the wake.
You, when are you going?
Wake?
Who died?
Clarissa's husband,
the father of your friend.
Didn't Joey tell you?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STAMMERS]
No, he's not...
What did you say?
Anyway, if you don't know,
I'll just text you
the details, okay?
I'm in a hurry.
I still have to pick up
what I'll bring to the wake.
Yes, you're right.
Okay, Yvette.
Thank you for letting me know.
Take care.
Okay, okay, bye.
Thanks!
[EXHALES]
Fake news.
Hon.
Oh, Hon?
Did I hear it right?
You're going to Delgado's wake?
Yes, Hon.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll go with you.
Okay, that's good.
I'm so happy
that you're coming with me.
Of course.
I also want to offer
condolences,
and I want to make sure
that everything is in order.
Okay then, Hon,
get dressed first.
- Okay.
- Okay, I'll just talk to nanny.
Nanny! Clara!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I really have somewhere to go.
If it's okay, stay with mommy.
Just tell me if something
happens to mommy.
I'll come back right away.
Of course, yes.
You know we need to do this,
so no one will ask
about dad anymore.
Condolence.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Why is it closed?
My daughter
and I can't bear to see
what happened to him.
Jin Ho is the enemy.
I knew it.
There's really something
about that man.
Jin Ho?
This seems old.
Did you get this
from the teddy bear?
Yes, Kisses found it.
Hopefully, it works.